厄尔 来玩"结婚 上床 或杀掉游戏之
Earl, time to play "Marry, sleep with, or kill:
餐厅版吧"
Diner edition."
一号卡座的妞们
Ladies, booth one?
上她 上她 上过她
Sleep with, sleep with, slept with.
厉害
Nice.
到你了 麦克斯 十号桌男的
Okay, Max, the dude at table ten.
有"丢食物进笼后就跑"的选项吗
Is there a "throw food in the cage and run" category?
过来参一脚
Hey, jump in.
我们在玩"结婚 上床 或杀掉游戏之
We're playing "Marry, sleep with, or kill:
餐厅版"
Diner edition."
不 如果我跟这餐厅里任何一人上过床
No, if I slept with anyone in this diner,
我会想杀了自己
I'd kill myself.
就算只是假设一下
Even in a fictional scenario,
我也不能这么无下限
I cannot permit myself to go there.
妹子 嗑药再兴奋都被你一扫而光了
Girl, you'd take the fun out of the punch bowl full of cocaine.
好吧 玩就玩
Okay, fine.
上厄尔 娶你
Sleep with Earl, marry you.
靠 别说我们啊
Not us! Jeez.
你是怪胎还是变态啊
What are you, a freak?
卡洛琳 你弄得人家好不舒服
I feel uncomfortable, Caroline.
人家都不知道怎么面对你了
Like, I don't know how to look at you anymore.
你在我心里变成穿怪怪女燕尾服的怪人了
Now, I can only see you in a creepy lady tux.
你自己说只是个游戏的
You said it was just a game!
我一点都不爱你 离我远点
I'm not in love with you. Back off!
厄尔 只是说着玩而已啦
It was just a joke, Earl.
亲爱的 开玩笑也要有个度
The things we say in jest, darling.
没度就是无下限啊
The things we say in jest.
天啊
Oh, my God,
你看同意出席开幕派对的人数
look at the RSVP list for our opening party.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店要塞不下啦
Max's homemade cupcakes is at capacity.
出席人数可能不止这些
Hey, we might even be overbooked,
根据我的经验 很多男的
because in my experience, even when guys
都说不会来[不射] 最后还不是都来了
say they're not going to come, they do.
卡洛琳 二号卡座等上菜
Caroline, booth two has been waiting
都等了足足10分钟了
for service for ten minutes!
阿憨绝对了解那烦躁感
And Han knows how frustrating that is,
因为他多年一直都等不到人"上"菜
'cause he's been waiting to be serviced for years.
虽然这完全不关你鸟事
Not that it's any of your business, Max,
但我可是有着丰富的性生活呢
but I have a very active sex life.
既然如此 阿憨你明天会带妞出席吗
So then, Han, will you be bringing a date tomorrow night?
不会...
Ah, no.
你知道"性爱"这事得有两个人吧
You do understand that sex involves two people, right?
而且你自己得是其中一个哦
And that one of those people has to be you?
一直说这些龌龊言语干嘛
What is all this dirty talk?
这里是餐厅 不是龌龊言语之地
This is a diner, not a dirty talking place.
抱歉 阿憨 我们知道自己还是员工
Sorry, Han, I know we still work here at night.
我立刻就去上菜
I'll go right over to the booth.
我们刚是在谈我们盛大的开幕派对
We were just talking about our big opening party.
你们整天就会说那"大开"幕
All you ever talk about is your big opening.
到底谁才龌龊啊
Now who has the potty mouth?
麦克斯 给我你的宾客名单
Max, I need your guest list names.
我还在等他们确认出席呢
Oh, okay, I'm still waiting for them to confirm,
先算个10个人吧
so just put me down for ten.
行 但是你得尽速给我名单
Okay, but I need their names ASAP.
我会把门禁搞得很严
I'm running a tight door.
我请了附近酒吧的保安来免费帮忙
I got a bouncer from a local club to donate his time.
我说我们是为湿疹病人做慈善募款
I told him it was a charity event for eczema.
干嘛 哪天功成名就了再捐一大笔钱嘛
What? We'll make a big donation when we're successful,
不过明天记得 有空就抓个几下痒哦
But, for tomorrow, every now and then, scratch a little?
各位 我有个大好新闻
Hi, everybody! I got great news.
你找出我们弄丢在"里面"的东西了吗
What? You finally found the thing we lost in there?
没呢 我当时就知道该拿线绑上
No. I knew we should've tied a string on it.
我收到了来自波兰的传真
No, look. I got a fax from Poland.
我的梦想豪宅盖好了 很厉害吧
My dream house is done! Isn't it amazing?
的确很厉害啊
It is amazing.
我都好几年没见过传真了
I haven't seen a fax in, like, five years.
苏菲 好漂亮啊
Sophie, it's so pretty!
你门廊上的那些木工活 超棒的啊
Look at all this sweet gingerbread woodwork on the porch.
我超兴奋的呢
Oh, I'm so excited.
等明天派对结束 我就搭机回国
I'm going to be on Air Poland flight right after big party.
你要回波兰 "新"闻啊
You are going to Poland? That's news.
你打算何时跟我说这事呢
And when were you going to tell me?
现在啊
Um, now, yeah.
我会回去一个月
Um, I'm going to be gone for a month.
好吧
Oh, okay.
休息一阵 不玩老玩的那
It will be good to have some time away
球加链也好
from the old ball and chain.
他不是在说我
Yah, he's not talking about me.
是说我们做爱时用的链球
We use a ball and chain in our lovemaking.
弄丢的就是那个玩意
That's the thing I can't find.
就这样吧
Okay, yeah.
好啦 我走了
Well, buh-bye.
明晚我的盛大告别派对上见啦
I'll see you tomorrow night at my big going away party!
苏菲 明晚是小蛋糕店的开幕派对
Sophie, the party's for our cupcake business.
瞧 所以说我太不喜欢你嘛
Oh, see, this is why I don't like you so much.
各位 谢谢你们的义务帮忙
Guys, thanks again for donating your time.
举办这样的隐睾症募款会
It's fundraisers like this that will help
病友们才能有免受苦难的一天
put an end to undescended testicles.
你好
H!
想见见这超牛逼 又超酷的
I'd like to meet the owner of this awesome
小蛋糕店的老板
and totally cool cupcake shop?
不用麻烦 因为老娘就是老板
Oh, nevermind! That's me.
麦克斯 你让人给你吹了头
Max, you got a blow-out!
是啊 我就想着去见识一下
Yeah, I'd figured I finally see
别人老说着的 去给人"吹"是怎样
what all the fuss about getting blown is.
您好 还没到我们开始宴客的时间呢
Oh, hi, we're not quite ready for guests yet.
女孩们 我是你们的门卫 涅维尔
Girl, I'm your doorman, Nevel.
抱歉 我还以为我们的门卫是...
Oh, I'm confused. I thought my doorman was--
无聊白人直男吗 本来是的
Straight, white, and boring? He was.
但是无聊男染上了流感
Then, boring came down with the flu.
所以就换成了又黑又基又不无聊的我啦
Now, you've got gay, black, and definitely not boring.
今晚是为什么疾病募款呢
So what's the charity tonight?
-湿疹 -隐睾症
- Eczema. - Undescended testicles.
为身染湿疹与患有隐睾症的人募款
People with eczema and undescended testicles.
神啊 这也太悲催太凄惨了吧
Lord, child. That is a cross to bear.
把宾客名单给我
Get me the door list,
赶紧帮这些可怜的蛋痒男募款治病吧
and let's make those poor, itchy boys some money.
又瞎编了一个慈善项目啊
Another fake charity?
你真有种[睾丸] 还是隐睾症的睾啊
You've got some balls, even if they aren't descended.
麦克斯 我们太幸运了
Max, we so lucked out.
有个毒舌基佬门卫
Nothing says "successful party"
最能显现派对办得很成功了
like a bitchy, gay doorman!
给我你邀请的宾客名单 我写下来
Give me your guest names. I'll write them down.
好吧 念给你
Okay, fine.
帮我写下 汤米 迪伦 罗比 强尼...
Put down Tommy, Dylan, Robbie, Johnny--
罗比跟强尼吗
Robbie and Johnny?
等等 麦克斯 这些全是你的前男友吗
Wait, Max, are these all your ex-boyfriends?
大概吧
Perhaps.
麦克斯 邀请的宾客
Max, the invited guests
应该全是有生意往来的朋友啊
were all supposed to be business contacts.
你看 所以我才不想太早告诉你
See, this is why I didn't tell you sooner.
你是个超级控制狂
You're a control freak.
而他们也都跟我的"生意本钱
And for the record, these guys have all had contact
有过往来"啊
with my business.
你是在用开幕派对
You're using our launch party
来羞辱你前男友们吗
to get back at ex-boyfriends?
废话
Uh, yeah!
成功不就是为了这个吗
That's what success is for,
让你可以对甩掉你的人说 "你去死吧"[吸它]
to say "suck it" to people who dumped you.
看到姐这美爆的秀发了吗 "你去死吧"
"See my blown-out hair? Suck it!
看到姐的超酷小蛋糕店了吗 "你去死吧"
"See my cool cupcake shop? Suck it!
看到姐衣服下的胸器了吗 你死都没得吸了
See these in this blouse? You wish you could suck it."
而且名单上不是只有我的前男友们
And here, it is not just boyfriends on my list.
我还邀请了文具店那
I also invited the lady from Staples
狗眼看人低的店员
who gives me attitude.
顺便也让"她去死吧"
She can suck it too.
行行行 但你邀请强尼夫妇来
Fine, but how is inviting Johnny
你是哪里比人家成功呢
and his new wife a victory?
就像这样
Oh, like this.
"你好啊 强尼太太 幸会幸会
"Hi, Mrs. Johnny. Nice to meet you.
你有渣男 姐有逼人胸器
You got him, but I got these
跟超酷小店 所以你去死吧
and all this, so suck it."
你这样有点神经吧
I'm not so sure this is healthy.
拜托哦
Are you kidding me?
这是我这辈子最不神经的一件事了
This is the healthiest thing I've done in my life.
我还想过邀请我妈来让她"去死吧"
I even thought about inviting my mother to come and suck it,
但这样她就知道我两年前留下的
but then she'd realize maybe I didn't commit suicide
自杀遗书是骗人的了
two years ago like my note said.
我准备好放人进来了
I'm about ready to open.
但我们不挂一些睾丸横幅
Shouldn't we be putting up some testicle banners,
或阴囊海报之类的吗
or scrotum posters, or something?
对了 外面有个超可爱的金发男找你
Also, there's a cute blonde boy out here asking for you
我都想"饿基扑男"了
that I'm about to eat alive.
安迪带免费酒吧的东西来了
That's Andy with the free bar stuff.
你先去吧 我在这待会儿
Go, I'm gonna stay here
多练习下等会要用的"你去死吧"脸
and practice my "Suck it" face for a while.
如何
How's this?
新弄的直发搭配你那脸
That look is so much more "suck it"
真是绝配啊
with the straight hair.
我也这么觉得
I know, right?
我可爱的男人来啦
There's my cute boyfriend. Hey.
去酒店买酒的过程如何
How did everything go at spike's liquor?
我去买的时候有点搞不清
Well, I got a little bit confused
我们要假装是哪种慈善活动
about what charity we're pretending to help,
我就跟店员说 我姐妹是流浪汉
so I told them my sister's homeless
隐睾症让我的蛋缩得老高
and my balls are up inside me.
只希望店员是真懂行 不是乱瞎扯了
Now, we just gotta hope spike's not the chatty type.
蛋蛋都回归原位了
Oh! They just dropped.
安迪 问你个问题
Hey, Andy, question.
你觉得我这是什么表情
What does this face say to you?
不知道 "我很酷"吗
I don't know, like, "I'm cool."
很接近了 再猜一次
So close! Guess again.
那是不是"我比你强"
Okay, like, "I'm better than you."
不对 是"老娘超屌 你去死吧"
No, like, "I'm it, and you can suck it."
没错没错 他们去死吧
Yes! Yes! They can suck it!
你今晚就穿这样吗
Is that what you're wearing tonight?
对啊... 不行吗
Yeah. No?
毛衣啊
A sweater?
我一直想着你今晚穿西装呢
I always saw you in a suit tonight.
快跑回家换套西装吧
Run home real quick and put on a suit.
快点 宾客很快要来了
Hurry, people are starting to come.
麦克斯还在做那副表情呢
Uh, Max is still making the face.
我知道 人家停不下来嘛
I know. I can't stop.
我这辈子都在等着做这表情呢
I've waited my whole life to make this face.
麦克斯 你瞧
Max, look.
我们的生意开张了
Our business is open.
等等 还差一点呢
Wait, wait, wait. Not quite.
倒数 五 四 三 二...
In five, four, three, two.
-您的名字 -苏菲·科臣斯基
- Name, please? - Sophie Kuchenski.
荣誉贵宾哦
Guest of honor.
您带了多少位[您派对有多少人]
How many in your party?
看 我就知道是我的派对
See, I knew it was my party!
麦克斯 队伍排满了整个走廊呢
Max, there's a line all the way down the hall
我都发出去快一百张名片了
And I've given out, like, a hundred business cards!
你知道这代表什么吗
You know what that means?
贫穷去死吧
Being poor can suck it!
女孩们 消防局的人刚来了
Girl, the fire marshal just dropped by,
说法规限制 里面宾客过多
and told me we can't let anymore people in
得走一批才能再进新的人
till some of these folks go out.
涅维尔 我邀请的人都还没进来呢
Nevel, none of my guests are even here yet.
所以你只能放那些看起来超帅
It is very important to let in any guy who looks hot,
但一看就会让你伤心的渣男进来
but you know would screw you over.
帅哥不都这么渣吗
Is there any other type?
我再进去拿点小蛋糕
I'll go get some more cupcakes.
宝贝 活动如何
Hey! How's it going so far, babe?
安迪 你这是干嘛
Andy, what are you doing?
我不是叫你回家换西装吗
I told you to come back in a suit.
是啊 但我就喜欢我身上这套
yeah, I know, but I like what I'm wearing.
你的意思是说 无论我多用力逼你
So you're telling me you'll just go and do what you want,
你就是打算不听话 随心所欲吗
no matter how much I try to control you?
是的
Yeah.
你这样真是帅爆了
That is so freaking hot.
卡洛琳
Caroline!
卡洛琳 他不让我进来
Caroline, I can't get in!
卡洛琳
Caroline!
少接点吻 多注意我啊
Less kissing, more noticing me!
我认识她 我的名字就在名单上
See, I know her, and my name's on the list.
李憨
Han Lee.
小可爱 就算我是个肥妞
Honey, if I was a fat girl,
而你的名字是叫李莎拉
and your name was Sara Lee,
我也不会发情放你进来
You still wouldn't be getting in.
里面满员了
We are at capacity!
我叫罗比 在名单上
Hey, Robbie. On the list.
快请进 小宝贝
Go right on in, child.
不是满员吗
Uh, hello?
要给你本字典 让你看看"满员"的意思吗
Do you need a dictionary to define the word "Capacity?"
我收到明确指示
I have clear orders:
性感的超帅渣男才放行
Only very hot men who look like trouble.
抱歉 请问麦克斯在哪
Excuse me, you know where I can find Max?
-她就在后头 -好的
- Yes, she's in the back. - Cool.
罗比 是我啊 卡洛琳
Robbie, it's me, Caroline.
抱歉 没认出来
Oh, sorry.
我们是不是上过床啊
Did we have sex?
什么 才没有呢
What? No!
我是麦克斯的室友
I'm Max's roommate.
麦克斯有过室友啊
Oh, Max had a roommate?
我当初真是整天都烂醉啊
I was pretty much wasted the whole time.
我几乎什么都记不得了
I remember, like, nothing,
我加入了戒酒协会 现在一天去一次
But I'm in the program now, so it's one day at a time.
-好吧 麦克斯就在里面 -谢了
- Well, Max is through there. - Cool.
但我们是上过床的对吧
But we did have sex, right?
才没有 我们没上过床
No! We did not have sex.
你邀过我 不过我对你没感觉
You offered, but I wasn't into you.
我会信才有鬼
Yeah, right.
-麦克斯 -罗比
- Hey, Max. - Robbie!
你干嘛摆这副表情
Why are you making that face?
你牙疼还是怎么了嘛
You have a toothache or something?
不是啊 只是我现在功成名就了
No, it's-I'm successful now
这是我开的店呢
and this is my shop.
哇 厉害啊
Wow. Cool.
我知道我之前是个酒鬼
So listen, I'm an alcoholic now,
做了很多不应该的事情
and I did a lot of stuff that wasn't cool,
我来是因为戒酒会让我来
and I came here because the program
为我以前的所作所为"餐会"
says that I have to make almonds.
"餐会"
"Almonds"?
你是说"忏悔"吗
You mean "Amends"?
好
Cool.
我知道我以前对你不忠
So, look, I cheated on you
每天都趁你不在时跟人乱搞
behind your back, like, every day.
我们可以不用现在搞忏悔
Well, um, we don't have to go into all this now.
我今晚很多事呢
It's kind of a big night for me.
还偷了你的钱
And I stole money from you too,
每次做爱完都偷你的钱
like, every time we had sex.
我们"做"了很多呢
but we had a lot of sex.
是啊
I know.
所以我也偷了你很多钱
Well, I stole a lot of money.
这下从"你去死吧"变成"我去死吧"
Well, this just went from "suck it" to "it sucks,"
把衣服掀起来
So lift up your shirt.
今晚总得捞点本回来
I gotta get something out of tonight.
我那些钱也算花得值了
Money well spent.
刚刚才知道我花在做爱上的钱
Just found out I paid for more sex
比一个阿拉伯商人还多
than an arab businessman.
或许我今晚不应该做这么神经的事
Maybe this wasn't the healthiest thing I could've done tonight.
那你打算怎么做
So what do you wanna do?
要不要让涅维尔别放强尼进来
Should I tell Nevel to keep Johnny out?
晚了 来不及了
Too late. Way too late.
麦克斯
Max.
好久不见
Hi.
你今晚比我记忆中的你还美
You look even better than I remember.
应该的 才让人吹的头呢
Well, I should. I just got blown.
你去死吧 你去死吧 你去死吧
Suck it, suck it, suck it, suck it.
麦克斯 你这小店太棒了
Max, this place is so awesome.
棒到像是在跟所有
It's like you're telling everybody
怀疑过你的人说 "你们去死吧"
who ever doubted you to suck it.
才没有 我们才没这么可悲
No, we're not petty like that.
里面有点吵
Hey, it's a little loud in here.
要不要去走廊上聊聊
You wanna talk in the hall?
让我看一眼我偌大的成功店面一眼
Uh, wait, let me take a look around my big, successful shop.
行 可以去一会
Yeah, I can go.
注意好麦克斯
Keep your eye on Max.
那戴着布拉德·皮特眼镜的男人伤过她心
That guy in the Brad Pitt glasses broke her heart,
我不信任那家伙
and I don't trust him.
麦克斯 你今晚真美
Max, you look insanely good.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
要不要把这句话对你老婆复诵一遍啊
Now, maybe you could repeat that to your wife,
她人呢
And where is she?
我没有跟她结婚
We never got married.
麦克斯 麦克斯 我进不去
Max! Max! I can't get in!
什么 你这没结过婚是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean you didn't get married?
强尼 强尼 我在这呢
Johnny! Hey, Johnny, I'm back here!
我不知道该不该对你说
I didn't know if I was gonna tell you,
然后又接到你的邀请函
but then I got your invite--
麦克斯 强尼 我在这呢
Max! Johnny! I'm back here!
要不要过去打个招呼
Should we just go say "hi"?
不必 现在没空
Uh, no, not right now.
麦克斯 麦克斯 我进不去
Max! Max! I can't get in!
麦克斯 强尼
Max! Johnny!
麦克斯 我一直很想你
Max, I've been thinking about you a lot.
停 在你说任何话之前
Stop. Before you say anything else,
我想说...
I just have to say
我要先吃糖
I need candy.
好了 你刚要说什么来着
All right, what were you saying?
我取消了婚礼 她不是我的真命天女
I called off the wedding because she wasn't the one,
想知道我从何得知吗
And you wanna know how I know that?
麦克斯 强尼
Max! Johnny!
我进不去派对现场
I can't get into the party!
过来
Come here.
帮帮我
Help me out!
求你了
Seriously!
那门卫就是一贱货
That doorman is a biatch!
好了 所以...
Okay, so, uh--
等等 我们在干嘛
Wait, what are we doing?
在放满糖果的房间里亲热
Making out in a room full of candy.
对哦
Right.
不行 不能这样
No, no, this can't happen.
我本来要给你我的"你去死吧"脸呢
I was gonna give you my "suck it" face.
行 对我做吧 我应得的
Okay, give it to me. I deserve it.
你的"你去死吧"脸好性感
Your "suck it" face is hot.
是发型的功劳
It's the hair.
我人生中最棒的一晚了
Greatest night of my life!
我声明 这不是我的T恤
Disclaimer: this is not my T-shirt,
当然 我也很支持女力的啦
Though I am all about the girl power.
我声明 这也不是我的T恤
Disclaimer: it's not my T-shirt either.
是某个书呆忘在洗衣店的
Some nerd left it in the dryer at the laundromat.
那件是我的
It's mine.
女力哦
Girl power!
不是吧 不是吧
No way. No way!
我闻到的是巧克力碎吗
Do I smell chocolate chips?
是安迪叔叔在做煎饼吗
And is uncle Andy making pancakes?
你没闻错 我也做了
You do, and I am.
兄台 虽然我不认识你
Dude, I don't know you,
但是巧克力碎煎饼超屌啊
but chocolate chip pancakes are the balls.
你们俩睡得如何
How did you two sleep?
哪有时间睡呀
Did we sleep?
很好 那接下来会如何呢
Great! So what's gonna happen now?
我是说今天店里的事
I meant today, at the shop,
我们隆重开业的首日呢
our big first day in business!
你们以为我是在说你们的关系吗
You thought I was talking about you two?
噗 我才懒得管你们俩
Plbbt! I don't care about you two.
噗 谁有空管你们俩啊
Plbbt! Nobody cares about you two.
首先 我们得先清理昨晚派对的垃圾
Well, first, we have to clean the party mess up.
昨晚我跟安迪打扫完了
Andy and I did it last night
在你不知去何处鬼混的时候
when you didn't come back.
某人是不是该放轻松点
Um, can someone here mellow out
塞点煎饼进她的"煎饼洞"里啊
and put some pancakes in her pancake hole?
没事 卡洛琳 我明白
No, Caroline, I get it.
我跟麦克斯一路以来的情路不顺
It's been a rocky ride for Max and me.
我跟她刚认识时 我有个女朋友
See, when we met, I had a girlfriend.
但他从来没告诉过她 然后...
Which he never told her about, and--
然后接着吃啊
And keep eating.
因为这样
and because of that,
我和麦克斯没有真正在一起过
Max and I never really got together,
而我也跟那女人分手了
and then that girl and I broke up,
后来再见到麦克斯时 我...
and by the time I saw Max again, I was--
订了婚准备结婚
Engaged to be married?
是的 我当时准备结婚了
Yeah, yeah, I was gonna get married.
等等 是跟之前那女朋友吗
Wait, to that same girlfriend?
不是的 另外一个
Different one. Different one.
但那事后来也没成
Yeah, but that didn't work out either,
之后我也再交过几个女朋友
and I've had a couple girlfriends since--
哟 还"几个"呢
Oh! Only a couple!
是啊 但是跟她们也一个都没成
Yeah, none of them seemed to work out.
她们都取代不了麦克斯
None of them are Max.
帮我留一个煎饼
Hey, save me a pancake.
卡洛琳好像想把它们统统吃光
It looks like Caroline has plans to eat them all.
麦克斯 你这个让人"去死吧"计划
Well, Max, as far as the "suck it" plan goes,
没让某人死成 还自己成了"你去吸吧"
it looks like somebody sucked something.
煎饼 煎饼洞
Pancakes, pancake hole.
他是个好人啦
He's a good guy.
他看起来不错啦
Yeah, he seems cool.
虽然常常坠入爱河 不过...
Kinda falls in love a lot, but hey...
我没叫他说这些
And I did not tell him to say that.
他从来不听我指挥 太性感了
He never does what I say. It's hot.
"不过"什么
"But hey" what?
还继续说啊
Oh, we're continuing?
我不知道怎么说
Um, I don't know.
我说可能有些偏颇 但麦克斯
Maybe I'm partial, but Max,
你是个"A"级姑娘
You're an "A."
而他感觉只是个"B"级男
He kind of seems like a "B."
是"B-"
Minus.
首先 看好了
First of all, look at me.
我这是"D"级胸器
I am clearly a "D,"
而且他也没有整天坠入爱河好吗
and I don't think he falls in love a lot.
天啊 我对煎饼爱爱爱不完
Man, I love, love, love pancakes.
如果可以 我真想娶个煎饼
If I could, I would marry a pancake.
几点了
What time is it?
开业首日嘛
Well, it's the first day open.
大家可能昨晚都玩太累了
All those people are probably tired from the party.
有道理
Yeah.
你看 我们也忘了打开这个
Oh, and look! We forgot to light it up.
人家不知道我们开门了
People don't know we're open.
倒数五 四 三 二...
In five, four, three, two.
上班吧
Go to work.
-第一天嘛 -是的
- First day! - Yep.
没人来
No one's here.
记得 我们一天只要卖70个小蛋糕
Remember: all we have to sell is 70 cupcakes a day
就能开下去了
to keep on track.
70个小蛋糕 不难嘛
70 cupcakes? That's not so hard.
我们再重开一次那灯吧
Maybe we should do the light again.
倒数五 四 三 二...
In five, four, three, two.
现在几点了
What time is it now?
明天 我们只需卖掉140个小蛋糕就行
Tomorrow, we only need to sell 140 cupcakes.
140个小蛋糕 不难嘛
140 cupcakes! That's not so hard.
我们今天卖掉了几个
How many did we sell today?
四个
Four.
都卖给强尼了
And all were to Johnny.
我觉得我犯了大错
I think I've made a terrible mistake.
才刚开始三天而已
It's only been three days.
生意会慢慢起步的
Business will pick up.
不 是跟强尼的事
No, with Johnny.
情况不同了 他现在是单身
It's different now that he's available.
说不定我是那种人
Maybe I'm the kind of person
只喜欢得不到的东西
who only wants something they can't have,
然后一旦得到又不喜欢了
and then when they get it, they don't want it anymore.
那你对我们的小蛋糕店也有这种感觉吗
Okay, but do you feel that way about the cupcake shop too?
没有 我爱我们的小蛋糕店
No, I love our cupcake shop.
哇 这是我第一次脱口说出
Wow, that's the first time I've ever said
我爱某样东西呢
I loved anything out loud,
我只对感冒糖浆说过[喝多会上瘾]
except for robitussin.
强尼来了
It's Johnny.
好吧 我知道我该怎么做
Well, I know what I have to do.
麦克斯 你不能现在反悔啊
Max, you can't change your mind about him now.
他是我们唯一的顾客
He's our only customer!
我一直以来都很喜欢他呢
By the way, I've always loved him.
你们好啊
Hey, guys.
我们能进厨房里谈谈吗
Um, could we talk in the kitchen?
等等 在你进去之前 我想说
Wait, before you go, I just wanna say
无论生活中发生了多少挫折
that no matter what goes down in life,
我们的店永远对你敞开
we are always open to your business.
我们不是要在疯狂地在厨房搞一炮
We're either gonna have crazy kitchen sex
就是我要被甩了
or I'm getting expelled.
我们不会在这搞一炮的
We're not having kitchen sex.
这里太脏了
It's way too dirty in here
被其他在这搞过的人弄得太脏了
from other people having kitchen sex.
所以就是我要被甩了
So I'm getting expelled?
我们俩很怪 很纠结对吧
It's weird, right? Between us?
是啊 我也不知道这算什么
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
可能是现在没有糖果雨之类的吧
Maybe it's an absence of a lot of candy...
但感觉就是不同了
but it's not the same.
麦克斯 强尼 我就觉得听到你们声音了
Max! Johnny! I thought I heard you.
麦克斯
Max!
我出不来啊
I can't get out!
或许只有在你有个女朋友时
Maybe we're only at our best
才是我们最适合的时候吧
when you have another girlfriend.
等你泡到新妞了再打给我吧
Maybe give me a call when you get that going
大概也就十分钟后的事
in, like, ten minutes.
或者在我婚礼当天打给你
Or I could just call you on my actual wedding day.
那也行啊
Oh, cool!
仪式前30分钟
Yeah, just call me 30 minutes
打给我 我会准时到场的
before the service, and I'll be there.
或者在你五十周年结婚纪念日打给我吧
Or better yet, call me at, like, your 50th wedding anniversary.
你这样才迷人嘛
Yeah, now that's hot.
麦克斯
Max!
强尼 我好冷
Johnny! I'm cold!
吻别吗
Kiss good-bye?
你们俩 我脚趾冻得没感觉了
Seriously, guys, I can't feel my toes!
你看 我们一分手 又来电了
See, it's hot again 'cause we broke up!
我的五十周年纪念见吧
I'll see you at my 50th,
或在那之前也行
If not before.
派对这么搞 现在又来
First the party, now this.
哪天我办派对 绝对不邀请你
When I have a party, you won't be on the list.
你说得对 那是我应得的惩罚
You're right. I deserve that.
别啊 我打算办一个街舞派对
No, I was doing a power move.
求你了 你一定得来啊
Please, I'm begging you to come.
再说吧
we'll see.
到时候我可能没空
I might be a little too busy
得忙我成功的小蛋糕店事业呢
with my big, successful cupcake shop,
所以你去死吧
So suck it.